Patti Cake$ is a music, drama film directed by Geremy Jasper.
Straight out of Jersey comes Patricia Dombrowski, a.k.a.
Killa P, a.k.a.
Patti Cake$, an aspiring rapper fighting through a world of strip
malls and strip clubs on an unlikely quest for glory.
Patricia Dombrowski, played by Danielle Macdonald.
Barb Dombrowski, played by Bridget Everett.
Jheri, played by Siddharth Dhananjay.
Basterd, played by Mamoudou Athie.
Nana, played by Cathy Moriarty.
Danny, played by McCaul Lombardi.
Patti Cakes (stylized as Patti Cake$) is a 2017 American
drama film directed by Geremy Jasper.
It was screened in the US Dramatic Competition section
of the 2017 Sundance Film Festival.
It was released on August 18, 2017, by Fox Searchlight Pictures.
The film explores themes of rap music, new jersey, aspiring musician.
The tone is emotional.